ILGWU Archives Department Collected Publications 5780/121 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- The Needle Point, 1954-1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: The Needle Point, Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
    By Wilkes-Barre Pittston District Council. Item is in English.
- New 1962 Disclosure Requirements, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Welfare and Pension Plan Disclosure Act as amended in 1962
  - Item 1: New 1962 Disclosure Requirements, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    By Commerce Clearing House. Welfare and Pension Plan Disclosure Act as amended in 1962. Item is in English.
- The New Gerrymander Threat, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Reprinted from The American Federationist, February 1971. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: The New Gerrymander Threat, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    By Daniel I. Wells; Gus Tyler. Reprinted from The American Federationist, February 1971. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- New York Supreme Court: Appellant's Brief, 1932; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Supreme Court: Appellant's Brief, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    By Emil Schlesinger; Abraham Schlesinger. Item is in English.
- New York Supreme Court: Respondent's Brief, 1945; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Supreme Court: Respondent's Brief, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    By Elias Lieberman. Item is in English.
- New York Supreme Court: Summons and Complaint, 1933; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Supreme Court: Summons and Complaint, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    By Carl J. Austrian; Joseph A. Broderick. Item is in English.
- News and Views. Nouvelles et Opinions., 1949-1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  English and French. No.1-2,5-6 (1949-1950); v.4:no.3 (1967)
  - Item 1: News and Views. Nouvelles et Opinions., Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    By Local 205. No.1-2,5-6 (1949-1950); v.4:no.3 (1967). Item is in English; French.
- Northeast Department 30th Anniversary, 1935-1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  32nd Convention, ILGWU, Miami Beach, Florida, May 17, 1965. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: Northeast Department 30th Anniversary, 1935-1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    By Northeast Department. 32nd Convention, ILGWU, Miami Beach, Florida, May 17, 1965. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- On the Avenue, 1940; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  v.2:no.2 (1940:Mar.)
  - Item 1: On the Avenue, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    By Local 38. v.2:no.2 (1940:Mar.). Item is in English.
- The Organizer, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  v.1 (1935)
  - Item 1: The Organizer, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    By Local 184. v.1 (1935). Item is in English.
- Our Aim, 1940-1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  v.5:no.44 (1940); v.10:no.98 (1948); v.11:no.103- 107 (1949-1950); v.13:no.112-115 (1950-1951); v.13:no.116-117 (1951); v.4:no.118-120,123,125,129-130,137-139,143 (1952-1957); v.5:no.149 (1958); v.7:no.165 (1962); v.8:no.169-170 (1963-1964); v.9:no.174 (19
  - Item 1: Our Aim, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    By Local 91. v.5:no.44 (1940); v.10:no.98 (1948); v.11:no.103-107 (1949-1950); v.13:no.112-115 (1950-1951); v.13:no.116-117 (1951); v.4:no.118-120,123,125,129-130,137-139,143 (1952-1957); v.5:no.149 (1958); v.7:no.165 (1962); v.8:no.169-170 (1963-1964); v.9:no.174 (19. Item is in English.
- Our Goal, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Our Goal, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Our Home; 1984 Year Book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Our Home; 1984 Year Book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
    By Louis Silver. Item is in English.
- Our Home; 1985 Year Book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Our Home; 1985 Year Book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Our Local 66, 1944-1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  v.3-23 (1944-1966). Not all issues present.
  - Item 1: Our Local 66, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
    By Local 66. v.3-23 (1944-1966). Not all issues present. Item is in English.
- Our Record, 1936; Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Official Bulletin, July 1936
  - Item 1: Our Record, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
    By Local 32. Official Bulletin, July 1936. Item is in English.
- Our Voice, 1935-1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  v.1-6 (1935-1949)
  - Item 1: Our Voice, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    By Chicago Joint Board. v.1-6 (1935-1949). Item is in English.
- The Pajama Game, 1954; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Script. Play performed at 1986 ILGWU convention. Especially adapted for ILGWU.
  - Item 1: The Pajama Game, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
    By George Abbott; Richard Bissell; Richard Adler; Jerry Ross. Script. Play performed at 1986 ILGWU convention. Especially adapted for ILGWU. Item is in English.
- The Pattern Maker, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  v.18:no.3-4 (1959:Mar.-Apr.)
  - Item 1: The Pattern Maker, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    By Pattern Makers' Guild. v.18:no.3-4 (1959:Mar.-Apr.). Item is in English.
- Playbill: Belasco Theatre, 1984; Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  ILGWU song "Look for the Union Label" opens second act of Accidental Death of an Anarchist. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: Playbill: Belasco Theatre, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
    ILGWU song "Look for the Union Label" opens second act of Accidental Death of an Anarchist. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Accidental Death of an Anarchist, 1984; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Script. Adapted by Richard Nelson from a literal translation by Suzanne Cowan. Revised October 1, 1984
  - Item 1: Accidental Death of an Anarchist, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By Dario Fo; Richard Nelson; Suzanne Cowan. Script. Adapted by Richard Nelson from a literal translation by Suzanne Cowan. Revised October 1, 1984. Item is in English.
- The Politics of Pat Moynihan, 1973; Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
  In The New Leader, v.56:no.7 (1973:Apr. 2)
  - Item 1: The Politics of Pat Moynihan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Gus Tyler. In The New Leader, v.56:no.7 (1973:Apr. 2). Item is in English.
- The Position of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union in Relation to CIO and AFL, 1934-1938, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Chronicled in Documents and Records
  - Item 1: The Position of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union in Relation to CIO and AFL, 1934-1938, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). Chronicled in Documents and Records. Item is in English.
- Der Preser, 1926-1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Yiddish. v.1-3 (1926-1928)
  - Item 1: Der Preser, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
    By Local 35. v.1-3 (1926-1928). Item is in Yiddish.
- Productivity and Incentives, 1977; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Productivity and Incentives, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
    By Mitchell Lokiec. Item is in English.
- Programa de Master en Adminstracion, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Programa de Master en Adminstracion, Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
    By IESA (Instituto de Estudios Superiores de Administracion). Item is in Spanish.
- Protocol of Peace, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Reprinted from American Labor Magazine, May 1968. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: Protocol of Peace, Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Reprinted from American Labor Magazine, May 1968. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- The Radical Myth-Makers, 1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
  In Dissent, Fall 1983. Book review. Photocopy.
  - Item 1: The Radical Myth-Makers, Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    By Gus Tyler. In Dissent, Fall 1983. Book review. Photocopy. Item is in English.
- Rank and File Cutter, 1941; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Election Issue 1941
  - Item 1: Rank and File Cutter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    By Local 10. Election Issue 1941. Item is in English.
- Real-Spot, 1938-1940; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  v.1:no.1 (1938:Nov.); v.2:no.2/3 (1939:Feb./Mar.); v.2:no.1 (1940:Jan.)
  - Item 1: Real-Spot, Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    By Allentown District Council. v.1:no.1 (1938:Nov.); v.2:no.2/3 (1939:Feb./Mar.); v.2:no.1 (1940:Jan.). Item is in English.
- Report of Educational Activities, 1922-1924, Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Report of Educational Activities, 1922-1924, Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Report of Proposed Revision of the Constitution and By-Laws of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Recommended to the 32nd Convention, Miami Beach, Florida, May 12, 1965
  - Item 1: Report of Proposed Revision of the Constitution and By-Laws of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). Recommended to the 32nd Convention, Miami Beach, Florida, May 12, 1965. Item is in English.
- Report of the General Executive Board to the 24th Convention, 1940; Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
  May 27-June 8, 1940. Carnegie Hall, New York City
  - Item 1: Report of the General Executive Board to the 24th Convention, Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
    By GEB (General Executive Board). May 27-June 8, 1940. Carnegie Hall, New York City. Item is in English.
- Report of the General Executive Board to the 32nd Convention, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
  May 12, 1965. Miami Beach, Florida
  - Item 1: Report of the General Executive Board to the 32nd Convention, Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
    By GEB (General Executive Board). May 12, 1965. Miami Beach, Florida. Item is in English.
- Reporter, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
  v.1:no.2 (1950:Nov.)
  - Item 1: Reporter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
    By Los Angeles Dress Joint Board. v.1:no.2 (1950:Nov.). Item is in English.
- Resolutions Introduced by the Delegates to the 34th Convention., 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Miami Beach, Florida, May 6, 1971. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: Resolutions Introduced by the Delegates to the 34th Convention., Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Miami Beach, Florida, May 6, 1971. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Schedule of Piece Work Prices for Cotton Dresses, 1938; Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Schedule of Piece Work Prices for Cotton Dresses, Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
    By Waist and Dressmakers' Joint Board. Item is in English.
- Schedule of Prices and Agreement, 1937; Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Schedule of Prices and Agreement, Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
    By Textile Workers' Organizing Committee. Item is in English.
- The Sephardic Home 37th Anniversary Journal, 1948-1985, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  37th Annual Dinner-Dance, November 2, 1985.
  - Item 1: The Sephardic Home 37th Anniversary Journal, 1948-1985, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    By Sephardic Home for the Aged. 37th Annual Dinner-Dance, November 2, 1985. Item is in English.
- The Shipping Clerk, 1954; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  v.2:no.1,3 (1954)
  - Item 1: The Shipping Clerk, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    By Local 60-A. v.2:no.1,3 (1954). Item is in English.
- Sing-A-Long With the ILGWU, 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Song book. 38th Convention, Hollywood, Florida, May 27, 1983. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: Sing-A-Long With the ILGWU, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Song book. 38th Convention, Hollywood, Florida, May 27, 1983. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Souvenir Journal Honoring Isidor Stenzor, 1962; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Souvenir Journal Honoring Isidor Stenzor, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    By Jewish Labor Committee. Item is in English.
- The Sportswear Worker, 1946; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  v.1:no.2 (1946:Apr.)
  - Item 1: The Sportswear Worker, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    By Local 226. v.1:no.2 (1946:Apr.). Item is in English.
- Spotlight on Local 48, ILGWU, 1956; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  English and Italian.
  - Item 1: Spotlight on Local 48, ILGWU, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
    By Local 48. Item is in English; Italian.
- Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1938; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  January 1, 1938 - December 31, 1938. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    By Auditing Department. January 1, 1938 - December 31, 1938. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1958; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  January 1, 1958 - December 31, 1958. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    By Auditing Department. January 1, 1958 - December 31, 1958. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1959; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  January 1, 1959 - December 31, 1959. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office.
  - Item 1: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    By Auditing Department. January 1, 1959 - December 31, 1959. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office.. Item is in English.
- Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1960; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  January 1, 1960 - December 31, 1960. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
    By Auditing Department. January 1, 1960 - December 31, 1960. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Statement on Behalf of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and Joint Board of Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions, 1915; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Statement on Behalf of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and Joint Board of Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    By Morris Hillquit. Item is in English.
- A Story About 50,000 New York Women, 1940; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A Story About 50,000 New York Women, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
    By Division of Women in Industry and Minimum Wage. Item is in English.
- The Story of Mary Brown, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Based on original text and idea by Leon Stein. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: The Story of Mary Brown, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    By Michael Johnson; James Corbett; Leon Stein. Based on original text and idea by Leon Stein. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- Supreme Court of New York County: Papers on Appeal From Order, 1931; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Supreme Court of New York County: Papers on Appeal From Order, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Supreme Court of New York County: Appellant's Reply Brief, 1940; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Supreme Court of New York County: Appellant's Reply Brief, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Samuel Hecht. Item is in English.
- Supreme Court of New York County: Brief of the Defendant-Respondent, Joint Board of the Dress and Waistmakers' Union of Greater New York, 1940; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Supreme Court of New York County: Brief of the Defendant-Respondent, Joint Board of the Dress and Waistmakers' Union of Greater New York, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Supreme Court of New York County: Papers on Appeal From Order, 1940; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Supreme Court of New York County: Papers on Appeal From Order, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Supreme Court of New York County: Plaintiffs' Trial Memorandum, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Supreme Court of New York County: Plaintiffs' Trial Memorandum, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Tailor's Progress: The Story of a Famous Union and the Men Who Made It, 1944; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Tailor's Progress: The Story of a Famous Union and the Men Who Made It, Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
    By Benjamin Stolberg. Item is in English.
- Technological Changes in the Garment Industry., 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  v.9 (1987:Feb.)
  - Item 1: Technological Changes in the Garment Industry., Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    By Mitchell Lokiec. v.9 (1987:Feb.). Item is in English.
- Thru the Needle's Eye, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  v.1:no.3 (1951:July/Aug.)
  - Item 1: Thru the Needle's Eye, Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
    v.1:no.3 (1951:July/Aug.). Item is in English.
- To Regulate the Textile Industry, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 22)
  May 19th, 1937
  - Item 1: To Regulate the Textile Industry, Publication (Box 5, Folder 22)
    By Committee on Labor. May 19th, 1937. Item is in English.
- Tomorrow is Beautiful, 1948; Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Special Labor Edition. Introduction by William Green
  - Item 1: Tomorrow is Beautiful, Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
    By Lucy Robins Lang; William Green. Special Labor Edition. Introduction by William Green. Item is in English.
- Toward Party Realignment, 1960; Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Reprinted from New Politics. Speech delivered at a conference of the Union Academy, November 1960. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: Toward Party Realighment, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
    By Gus Tyler. Reprinted from New Politics. Speech delivered at a conference of the Union Academy, November 1960. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Trends and Prospects in the Women's Garment Industry, 1965-1968, Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Report presented by GEB to the 33rd ILGWU Atlantic City Convention, May, 1968. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: Trends and Prospects in the Women's Garment Industry, 1965-1968, Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
    Report presented by GEB to the 33rd ILGWU Atlantic City Convention, May, 1968. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- Trends and Prospects Women's Garment Industry, 1959-1962, Publication (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Report presented by GEB to the ILGWU Atlantic City Convention, May, 1962. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: Trends and Prospects Women's Garment Industry, 1959-1962, Publication (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Report presented by GEB to the ILGWU Atlantic City Convention, May, 1962. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of ILGWU Locals 137-140-143, 1933-1958, 1985; Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Yonkers State Armory, October 25, 1958
  - Item 1: Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of ILGWU Locals 137-140-143, 1933-1958, Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
    By Locals 137-140-143. Yonkers State Armory, October 25, 1958. Item is in English.
- U.S. Production, Imports and Import/Production Ratios for Cotton, Wool and Man-Made Fiber Textiles and Apparel, 1985; Publication (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: U.S. Production, Imports and Import/Production Ratios for Cotton, Wool and Man-Made Fiber Textiles and Apparel, Publication (Box 5, Folder 28)
    By International Trade Administration. Item is in English.
- The Union Guide, 1934-1938; Publication (Box 5, Folder 29)
  v.1:no.1 (1934:Dec. 6) - v.3:no.1 (1938:Feb.). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: The Union Guide, Publication (Box 5, Folder 29)
    By Locals 150-157. v.1:no.1 (1934:Dec. 6) - v.3:no.1 (1938:Feb.). Bound volume. Item is in English.
- Union News, 1956; Publication (Box 5, Folder 30)
  v.4:no.10,12 (1956)
  - Item 1: Union News, Publication (Box 5, Folder 30)
    By Dress Joint Board. v.4:no.10,12 (1956). Item is in English.
- Union Progress, Publication (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Union Progress, Publication (Box 5, Folder 31)
    By Local 114. Item is in English.
- United We Stand, 1944; Publication (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Buffet Supper, Kansas City USO, January 16, 1944
  - Item 1: United We Stand, Publication (Box 5, Folder 32)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). Buffet Supper, Kansas City USO, January 16, 1944. Item is in English.
- Victoire, 1941-1942; Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  French and English. Victory. v.1 (1941-1942)
  - Item 1: Victoire, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). Victory. v.1 (1941-1942). Item is in English; French.
- Voice of 89, 1980; Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
  v.1:no.1 (1980:Dec.)
  - Item 1: Voice of 89, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
    By Local 89. v.1:no.1 (1980:Dec.). Item is in English.
- The Voice of Local 144, 1938; Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  English and Italian. Christmas Issue, v.1:no.11 (1938:Dec.)
  - Item 1: The Voice of Local 144, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    By Local 144. Christmas Issue, v.1:no.11 (1938:Dec.). Item is in English; Italian.
- Welcome, Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Welcome, Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
    By Louis Stulberg. Item is in English.
- What Now!, 1936; Publication (Box 5, Folder 37)
  v.1:no.3 (1936:Feb. 21); v.1:no.7 (1936:Mar. 19)
  - Item 1: What Now!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 37)
    By Local 884. v.1:no.3 (1936:Feb. 21); v.1:no.7 (1936:Mar. 19). Item is in English.
- Why FOUR?, Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Why FOUR?, Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
    By FOUR (Federation of Union Representatives). Item is in English.
- The Work Ethic: A Union View, 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Chapter 10 in The Work Ethic: A Critical Analysis. Photocopy. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: The Work Ethic: A Union View, Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
    By Gus Tyler. Chapter 10 in The Work Ethic: A Critical Analysis. Photocopy. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Workers Defense League: Fourty-Seventh Anniversary Journal, 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 40)
  47th Anniversary Journal In Honor of the Memory of David Dubinsky. October 20, 1983.
  - Item 1: Workers Defense League: Fourty-Seventh Anniversary Journal, Publication (Box 5, Folder 40)
    By Workers Defense League. 47th Anniversary Journal In Honor of the Memory of David Dubinsky. October 20, 1983. Item is in English.
- Your Union: a Handbook of Information for ILGWU Members in Wyoming Valley District Council, Publication (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Your Union: a Handbook of Information for ILGWU Members in Wyoming Valley District Council, Publication (Box 5, Folder 41)
    By Northeast Department. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Der Yunion Arbeyter, 1925-1926; Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
  Yiddish. v.1 (1925-1926). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: Der Yunion Arbeyter, Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
    By Union Worker Group. v.1 (1925-1926). Bound volume. Item is in Yiddish.
- Der Yunion Arbeyter, 1925-1926; Publication (Box 5, Folder 43)
  Yiddish. v.1 (1925-1926). Bound volume. 2nd copy.
  - Item 1: Der Yunion Arbeyter, Publication (Box 5, Folder 43)
    By Union Worker Group. v.1 (1925-1926). Bound volume. 2nd copy. Item is in Yiddish.
- The Blouse Maker, 1958; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  v.1:no.1 (1958:Feb.)
  - Item 1: The Blouse Maker, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    By Local 25. v.1:no.1 (1958:Feb.). Item is in English.
- The Cloakmaker, 1963-1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Cloakmaker, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
    By Los Angeles Cloak Joint Board. Item is in English.
- Chicago Women's Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  v.10:no.1-2 (1923)
  - Item 1: Chicago Women's Garment Worker, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    By Chicago Joint Board Cloak Skirt and Dress Workers' Union. v.10:no.1-2 (1923). Item is in English.
- Gerechtigkeit, 1923; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Yiddish. v.5:no.34 (1923:Aug.). Photocopy of one article.
  - Item 1: Gerechtigkeit, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). v.5:no.34 (1923:Aug.). Photocopy of one article. Item is in Yiddish.
- Good News, 1943; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  v.1:no.1 (1943:Mar. 24)
  - Item 1: Good News, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    By Sterling-Reliance Workers. v.1:no.1 (1943:Mar. 24). Item is in English.
- In Der Arbeyter Welt, 1930-1939; Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Yiddish. Photocopies of a column from Der Tog, various dates.
  - Item 1: In Der Arbeyter Welt, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)